uploking.com 2013-01-31

# UploKing.com - Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY

UploKing (the “Site”) and (Collectively “UploKing”) ”) takes all necessary steps to protecting the interest of all our users and their vital information while using our file hosting and online storage. Therefore this Statement of Privacy Policy governs all the data collection and usage of the Site. It does not govern personal information collected by UploKing offline, or web pages having separate privacy policies or not linking to this Privacy Policy. You will find that we have adopted the following provisions to comply with both international regulations dealing with Privacy and Data Protection, as well the requirements to comply with the EU Directive 95/46/EC (as amended). By accessing, registering, transacting, downloading, uploading and/or using UploKing, you consent to the data practices described in this Statement. Furthermore it is your legal obligation to review all aspects to this policy and acknowledge the legal rights of your privacy being protected.

Usage Collection & Information Disclosure:

Upon subscribing with the Site you will find that we will collecta mandatory email address without any confirmation and that we may also collect your full-name, email address, and password with the effect of registering on signup with UploKing. Occasionally we may collect from time to time various anonymous demographics that may be used for any promotional campaigns with UploKing or to contact you in the near future. Additionally we may automatically collect information which pertains to your computer hardware and software. This information can and may include: IP addresses, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation to maintain the quality of service, and to provide general statistics regarding the use of the Site and in connection with all users that download files. Furthermore, please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through the Site or through any social postings and/or testimonies on the Site or other websites, that information may be collected by others. WE DO NOT (SELL, RENT OR LEASE) CUSTOMER LISTS TO THIRD PARTIES.

All payment information will be confined to an online transaction gateway or through SMS payments available on the Site such as Textnation.com, besides the general legalities that govern (AdworkMedia.com and Paguelofacil.com) and their collection practices used during the processing of your transactions, besides the use of direct debit for our EU consumers using the Site. Therefore UploKing has no other affiliation with AdworkMedia.com and Paguelofacil.com, along with SMS payments from Textnation.com except for transactions, for any affiliation with any third party links or financial facilities. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future and/or change and add additional payment methods.

We do not knowingly collect information online or offline pertaining to minors under the age of 13, and you will find that we are compliant with the laws that govern the usage and collection of information regarding the consent of minors regulated under the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) and the Children's Internet Protection Act of 2001 (CIPA).Furthermore you will find that we will purge any personal identifiable information that may pertain to Children under the age of 13 if we become aware of this or through the fact of acknowledgement from a parent or guardian that has contacted us through email below.

We will without a doubt disclose all personal information, without notice, only if requested to do so by law or in such belief necessary through good faith that such action is to:

    Conform to all edicts of the law and/or to comply with any or all legal processes served on UploKing and/or the “Site”;  
    To protect and defend the legal rights or property of UploKing and/or the “Site”; and  
    Act under all exigent circumstances that govern the personal protection and safety of its users using UploKing and/or the “Site”, or the public.

Cookie Usage & Collection:

We may use the use of “Cookies”, which therefore implements the collection, usage and storage of cookies with your absolute consent. You will find that cookies are uniquely assigned to you and can only be read through a web server, which cannot be used to run any programs or deliver any viruses to your computer. Therefore each user has the ability to accept or decline cookies when using the Site, but you may not be able to experience all the features of the Site, if you deem to decline the usage of cookies.

Personal Security:

Your personal information is secure when using UploKing and/or the “Site” from unauthorized access, and/or use of disclosure. When personal information is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. We maintain our Site each and every day to secure any loop holes or legal structures that may need attention, making it safe for you to register with us and/or make payment transactions. However, we expect that you will always take all extra precautions of securing your personal identifiable information through the use of the “Site” or any other website that you tend to use.

Modifications & Changes:

UploKing does make modifications and/or changes to reflect certain legislation from time to time in order to be compliant within this Statement of Privacy and use of the Site. Therefore we encourage that all users review this Statement of Privacy periodically to see how we are maintaining to protect your rights and obligations as laws may change or the “Site” changes.

Comments & Concerns:

We appreciates any comments and/or concerns that you may have regarding this Statement of Privacy and the usage of UploKing, and/or if you believe that we have not adhered to this Statement, you may contact us through email at: contact@UploKing.com.
